C:\Projects\DAO\archid\addin\module\override\	af_archid_en-us.tlk
6610000	The Archid mod is a compilation of other mods plus some custom content. Some of the external mods have been imported in to allow them to be merged together.
6610001	No Helmet Rulebook
6610002	The character using this book will toggle on/off helmet graphics.
6610003	"WARNING!  The No_Helmet_Hack module failed to hide the helmets.  This is likely due to an incompatibility with a loaded module.  Possible solutions:
1)  Check the My Documents/Bioware/Packages/Core/Overrides file for any BITM_* file.  Delete it if there is, as this would be the likely conflicting mod.
2)  Remove this mod and reinstall it as the last mod
3)  Remove other mods until this mod succeeds.  Suspect mods that change item properties.
4)  Download and install the master override file."
6610004	Grey Warden Heavy Boots
6610005	Heavy boots made by Grey Warden Smiths specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Warriors.
6610006	Grey Warden Arcane Boots
6610007	Arcane boots made by Grey Warden Enchanters specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Mages.
6610008	Grey Warden Commander Boots
6610009	Massive boots made by Grey Warden Mastersmiths specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Commanders.
6610010	Blighted Grey Warden Commander Boots
6610011	"When the darkspawn taint gets into contact with any material, it will corrode them and turning them into a blighted variant of itself if not regularly cleaned.

This has happened to this pair of boots. Being worn by grey wardens for long periods of time with constant exposure to the darkspawn taint whether it is from the blood or from the wearer itself, corrode the metal parts and the cloth materials into a twisted reflection of what they once were."
6610012	Grey Warden Scout Boots
6610013	Medium boots made by Grey Warden Tailors specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Scouts.
6610014	Grey Warden Heavy Armour
6610015	Heavy armour made by Grey Warden Smiths specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Warriors.
6610016	Grey Warden Arcane Robes
6610017	Arcane robes made by Grey Warden Enchanters specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Mages.
6610018	Grey Warden Commander Armour
6610019	Massive armour made by Grey Warden Mastersmiths specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Commanders.
6610020	Blighted Grey Warden Commander Armour
6610021	"When the darkspawn taint gets into contact with any material, it will corrode them and turning them into a blighted variant of itself if not regularly cleaned.

This has happened to this armour. Being worn by grey wardens for long periods of time with constant exposure to the darkspawn taint whether it is from the blood or from the wearer itself, corrode the metal parts and the cloth materials into a twisted reflection of what they once were."
6610022	Grey Warden Scout Armour
6610023	Medium suits made by Grey Warden Tailors specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Scouts.
6610024	Grey Warden Heavy Gloves
6610025	Heavy gloves made by Grey Warden Smiths specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Warriors.
6610026	Grey Warden Arcane Gloves
6610027	Arcane gloves made by Grey Warden Enchanters specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Mages.
6610028	Grey Warden Commander Gloves
6610029	Massive gloves made by Grey Warden Mastersmiths specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Commanders.
6610030	Blighted Grey Warden Commander Gloves
6610031	"When the darkspawn taint gets into contact with any material, it will corrode them and turning them into a blighted variant of itself if not regularly cleaned.

This has happened to this pair of gloves. Being worn by grey wardens for long periods of time with constant exposure to the darkspawn taint whether it is from the blood or from the wearer itself, corrode the metal parts and the cloth materials into a twisted reflection of what they once were."
6610032	Grey Warden Scout Gloves
6610033	Medium gloves made by Grey Warden Tailors specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Scouts.
6610034	Grey Warden Heavy Helmet
6610035	Heavy helmets made by Grey Warden Smiths specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Warriors.
6610036	Grey Warden Arcane Hood
6610037	Arcane hoods made by Grey Warden Enchanters specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Mages.
6610038	Grey Warden Commander Helmet
6610039	Massive helmets made by Grey Warden Mastersmiths specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Commanders.
6610040	Blighted Grey Warden Commander Helmet
6610041	"When the darkspawn taint gets into contact with any material, it will corrode them and turning them into a blighted variant of itself if not regularly cleaned.

This has happened to this helmet. Being worn by grey wardens for long periods of time with constant exposure to the darkspawn taint whether it is from the blood or from the wearer itself, corrode the metal parts and the cloth materials into a twisted reflection of what they once were."
6610042	Grey Warden Scout Hood
6610043	Medium hoods made by Grey Warden Tailors specially designed to be worn by Grey Warden Scouts.
6610044	Grey Warden Shield
6610045	"The Shield of the Grey Wardens, marked with the stamp of the griffon upon its surface."
6610046	Grey Warden Staff
6610047	"The Magic Staff of the Grey Wardens, marked with the shape of the griffon upon its head."
6610048	Grey Warden Dagger
6610049	"The Dagger of the Grey Wardens, marked with the stamp of the griffon upon its blade."
6610050	Grey Warden Greatsword
6610051	"The Greatsword of the Grey Wardens, marked with the stamp of the griffon upon its blade."
6610052	Grey Warden Longsword
6610053	"The Longsword of the Grey Wardens, marked with the stamp of the griffon upon its blade."
6610054	Grey Warden Longbow
6610055	"The Longbow of the Grey Wardens, marked with the stamp of the griffon upon its wooden surface."
6610056	Alistair's Rose
6610057	"A beautiful rose with velvety petals of deep red. This was a gift from Alistair.

Whether infused with lyrium, magically preserved, or just the perfect cultivar for cut flower arrangements, the enduring loveliness of this single perfect bloom serves as a reminder that rare and wonderful things can indeed be found amidst all the darkness."
6610058	Cord of the Beresaad
6610059	"Intricately braided of many thin leather strands, this sturdy torc is otherwise unornamented."
6610060	Armour of the Sten
6610061	"Traditionally worn by a Sten of the Berasaad, this armour is light and functional for the protection it offers.
Finely linked chainmail, exotic hardened leather plates, and carefully ornamented metals show the craftsmanship that went into this piece.
As Qunari do not go by names, it is impossible to trace the origin of this armour, though it looks to have seen use in combat."
6610062	Branch of the Cursed Tree Barnstokkr
6610063	"This twisted length of wood, carved with strange symbols, is one of the branches of the legendary Barnstokkr, a cursed tree located south of Kokari Wilds, in lands unknown. The legend says that the tree is doomed to burn forever because of a curse invoked by a witch who, before dying, killed all the Templars that was hunting, causing a huge explosion of flames malignant, near the oldest tree the forest where she lived. Since then, the tree burns eternally in these flames that are full of hatred, bitterness and rage. Probably, the symbols that were carved on the branch, used to contain and control the terrible evil energy emanating from these flames. Do not want to know where your Mabari found this branch, much less whom he belonged."
6610064	...
6610065	There is a vial tied to the birds leg… <act>Try to take it!</act>
6610066	<act>Leave the bird alone.</act>
6610067	"Suddenly, you seem to know a lot more about ..."
6610068	<act>Look into the raven's eyes</act>
6610069	Assassin
6610070	Bard
6610071	Berserker
6610072	Ranger
6610073	Shapeshifter
6610074	Spirit Healer
6610075	Templar
6610076	... especially the ways of the ...
6610077	Warriors
6610078	Mages
6610079	Rogues
6610080	"<title>Do not drink it!</title>
An exotic venom from far away lands erases good and bad memories alike."
6610081	Potion of Respecialization
6610082	Raven
6610083	Ugh.. Where am I?!
6610084	Ooh! I feel... different!
6610085	Something is strange...
6610086	"This isn't right! No, no, nono!"
6610087	What... Who the... What just happened?!
6610088	Hamsters and rangers everywhere!
6610089	"! WARNING !
Respecializing your character can have unforseen implications! Always make sure that you have saved your progress before attempting to use this potion.

Are you sure you want to respecialize this character?"
6610090	"Thank you for downloading Character Respecialization v1.6!
The module is now installed and working properly!"
6610091	Drink me!
6610092	Spell Shaping
6610093	"When active, the caster will shape and direct wide-area spells to avoid friendly fire at a cost of additional mana. Party members gain protection from the damage, with the additional mana spent based on the number of allies in the target area."
6610094	Improved Spell Shaping
6610095	"Party members gain protection from the secondary effects of friendly spells such as knockdown, freezing and slow movement rate."
6610096	Expert Spell Shaping
6610097	Friendly fire damage protection is extended to all allies on the battlefield.
6610098	Master Spell Shaping
6610099	Allies and party members no longer experience any damage or secondary effects from friendly wide-area spells.
6610100	Warning: Spell Shaping Mod has detected a compatibility issue with one of the mods you have installed. Spell Shaping may not work properly.
6610101	"<name/> (<guitypename/>)
<usetype/>

<description/>"
6610102	"<name/> (<guitypename/>)
<usetype/>
Range: <range/>
Activation: <cost/>
Cooldown: <cooldown/>s

<requirements/>

<description/>"
6610103	"<name/> (<guitypename/>)
<usetype/>
Range: <range/>
Activation: <cost/>
Cooldown: <cooldown/>s

<description/>"
6610104	"Shale activates a mode that focuses on offense, taking penalties to defense and armor in exchange for bonuses to damage and attack. Slam, Quake, and Killing Blow add bonuses to this mode."
6610105	"Shale slams a stony fist into the enemy target. If the blow connects, it generates an automatic critical hit and knocks the target back. The target is also stunned briefly unless it passes a physical resistance check. After learning this talent, Shale gains bonuses to damage, attack, and armor penetration whenever Pulverizing Blows is active."
6610106	"Shale strikes the ground repeatedly, sending out multiple shockwaves. Nearby creatures take damage and are knocked to the ground unless they pass a physical resistance check. They are also slowed briefly unless they pass another physical resistance check. After learning this talent, Shale gains a bonus to movement speed, while suffering a greater penalty to defense, whenever Pulverizing Blows is active."
6610107	"Shale focuses strength into one devastating blow against an enemy. This attack gains bonus armor penetration and is an automatic critical hit if it connects. If the target has less than 50% health, this attack inflicts increasing damage as the target’s health diminishes. Shale suffers penalties to attack and stamina regeneration for a short time after using this attack. After learning this talent, Shale gains bonuses to damage, attack, armor penetration, and critical chance whenever Pulverizing Blows is active."
6610108	"Shale activates a mode that focuses on defense, gaining bonuses to armor, physical, and elemental resistances, while suffering penalties to damage and critical chance. Whenever this mode is active, Shale’s threat toward all nearby enemies increases over time, making them more likely to target Shale. Bellow, Stone Will, and Regenerating Burst add bonuses to this mode."
6610109	"Shale erupts with the sound of the Rock itself, stunning nearby enemies unless they pass a mental resistance check against Shale’s constitution. They are also dazed, and suffer penalties to attack and defense, unless they pass another mental resistance check against Shale’s constitution. Enemies stunned by this attack cannot resist being dazed. The power of this talent depends on Shale's constitution. This talent increases the bonuses of Stoneheart."
6610110	"Shale attracts the attention of a single enemy, who now views Shale as the most urgent threat on the battlefield and is likely to target Shale. After this talent is learned, Stoneheart will also give Shale bonuses to health regeneration and stamina regeneration, and enemies are even more likely to target Shale when that mode is active."
6610111	"Shale explodes with energy, damaging all nearby enemies. Enemies hit by the explosion are knocked down or knocked back unless they pass a physical resistance check against Shale’s constitution. They are also stunned unless they pass a mental resistance check against Shale’s constitution. The energy gives Shale a burst of health regeneration and stamina regeneration. The lower Shale's health or stamina, the stronger the regeneration. The power of this talent also depends on Shale's constitution. This talent further increases the bonuses of Stoneheart."
6610112	"Shale activates a mode that enables long-range attacks, gaining a large defense bonus against missile attacks while suffering penalties to attack and movement speed. While in this mode, Shale emanates an aura that grants nearby party members bonuses to ranged critical chance and ranged attack speed. Hurl Rock, Earthen Grasp, and Rock Barrage add bonuses to this mode."
6610113	"Shale pulls a rock from the ground and hurls it to a location, dealing physical damage to all creatures in the impact area. Creatures closer to the center of the impact take more damage, and those within 3 meters of the center are also knocked down unless they pass a physical resistance check against Shale's strength. Friendly fire possible. This talent increases the bonuses for party members and Shale’s missile deflection."
6610114	"Shale pounds the earth, immobilizing enemies unless they pass a physical resistance check, in which case they suffer penalties to attack speed and movement speed instead. Shale’s willpower increases the duration of the effects. This talent further increases Shale’s missile deflection."
6610115	"Shale tosses up multiple rocks that crash down in the targeted area. Creatures within the area take damage and are knocked down or knocked back unless they pass a physical resistance check. Friendly fire possible. This talent increases the bonuses for party members and Shale’s missile deflection. Nearby party members now also gain bonuses to attack and damage when using ranged weapons. Additionally, Shale’s aura can now shield others, granting party members within 3 meters a bonus to missile deflection."
6610116	"Shale activates a support mode that imbues nearby party members with bonuses to defense, armor, and all resistances. Shale is immobilized when in this mode, suffering a penalty to defense while gaining bonuses to armor, physical, spell, and elemental resistances. Inner Reserves, Renewed Assault, and Supernatural Resilience add bonuses to this mode."
6610117	"Whenever Stone Aura is active, party members within the aura now receive bonuses to health regeneration, stamina regeneration, and spellpower. This talent also increases the radius of Stone Aura."
6610118	"Whenever Stone Aura is active, Shale gains additional bonuses to armor, spell, and elemental resistances. Party members within the aura gain additional bonuses to health regeneration, stamina regeneration, and spellpower, as well as a bonus to movement speed. This talent also increases the radius of Stone Aura."
6610119	"Whenever Stone Aura is active, Shale gains additional bonuses to armor, physical, spell, and elemental resistances. Party members within the aura gain additional bonuses to defense, armor, and all resistances. The aura now also grants additional bonuses to party members when they stay close to Shale. This talent also increases the radius of Stone Aura."
6610120	Bonuses to damage and attack; penalties to defense and armor (Slam: bonus to armor penetration; Quake: bonus to movement speed).
6610121	Knocked down; possible penalty to movement speed.
6610122	Shale suffers reduced attack and stamina regeneration. Target is knocked down or knocked back.
6610123	"Bonuses to armor, physical, and elemental resistances; penalties to damage and critical chance (Stone Will: bonus to health regeneration and stamina regeneration)."
6610124	Stunned; possible penalties to attack and defense.
6610125	"Shale gains increased health regeneration and stamina regeneration. Enemies are knocked down, knocked back, or stunned."
6610126	"Shale gains increased missile deflection, but suffers reduced movement speed and attack. Party members gain bonuses to ranged critical chance and aim speed."
6610127	Paralyzed; penalties to attack speed and movement speed.
6610128	Knocked down or knocked back.
6610129	"Shale is paralyzed but gains bonuses to armor and resistances. Party members gain bonuses to defense, armor, and resistances."
6610130	Bonuses to ranged attack and damage; possible bonus to missile deflection.
6610131	"Bonuses to defense, armor, resistances, and spellpower."
6610132	Stone Will
6610133	"With a will of stone, Shale becomes a living fortress. All active movement speed modifiers are immediately removed. For a time, Shale gains increased physical and mental resistances, and becomes immune to knockdown, knockback, and slip effects. All incoming damage is partially absorbed, until a maximum amount is reached. Shale is slowed during this time, but will also shrug off any incoming effect that would alter movement speed. The power of this talent depends on Shale's constitution. After this talent is learned, Shale gains bonuses to health regeneration and stamina regeneration whenever Stoneheart is active, and enemies are even more likely to target Shale."
6610134	"Bonuses to physical and mental resistances; incoming damage is partially absorbed; immune to knockdown, knockback, slip, and movement speed modifications."
6610135	"With a will of stone, Shale becomes a living fortress. All active movement speed modifiers are immediately removed. For a time, Shale gains increased physical and mental resistances, and becomes immune to knockdown, stun, and slip effects. All incoming damage is partially absorbed, until a maximum amount is reached. Shale is slowed during this time, but will also shrug off any incoming effect that would alter movement speed. The power of this talent depends on Shale's constitution. After this talent is learned, Shale gains bonuses to health regeneration and stamina regeneration whenever Stoneheart is active, and enemies are even more likely to target Shale."
6610136	"Bonuses to physical and mental resistances; incoming damage is partially absorbed; immune to knockdown, stun, slip, and movement speed modifications."
6610137	Arcane Unlock
6610138	A short burst of arcane magic will deal with most simple locks.
6610139	Finesse Unlock
6610140	More stubborn locks require some finesse. This spell is able to manipulate some of the inner components allowing opening of more complex locks.
6610141	Power Unlock
6610142	"This spell allows you to channel more of your power into the lock, opening more complex varieties."
6610143	Spell too weak to unlock
6610144	Lock cannot be unlocked with magic
6610145	Wrong type of target to unlock
6610146	Target already unlocked
6610147	Party Storage Chest
6610148	"The Extra Dog Slot (EDS) Mod has detected a minor conflict with another mod.

EVENT_TYPE_SUMMON_DIED is not getting routed to EDS. As a result, when summoned creatures die, the dog will not shift up to the uppermost summon slot. You will have to blow the whistle to re-summon the dog and shift the dog up manually."
6610149	"The Extra Dog Slot (EDS) Mod has detected a conflict with another mod that you have installed.

EVENT_TYPE_DYING is not getting routed to EDS. As a result, when the owner of the dog dies, the dog will die as well and the portrait will disappear. If this happens, you will have to blow the whistle following combat to dismiss and then summon the dog."
6610150	"The Extra Dog Slot (EDS) Mod has detected a conflict with another mod that you have installed.

EVENT_TYPE_PARTY_MEMBER_FIRED is not getting routed to EDS. As a result, you should make sure you blow the whistle and remove the dog BEFORE the game removes the party, or you may break the game.  Here is a known list of offending locations (you should probably write these down):
Red Cliff:  When entering the fade to save the boy
Circle OF Magi: When entering the fade because of the sloth demon on the 4th floor
Orzamar : The provings.  Each round removes the party members
Denerim : At the pearl. If you sleep with anyone, the party is removed.
Denerim: If you win the lands meet and chose a 1 on 1 match with Logain."
6610151	"The Extra Dog Slot (EDS) Mod has detected a conflict with another mod that you have installed.

EVENT_TYPE_DYING is not getting routed to EDS. As a result, when the owner of the dog dies, the dog will die as well and the portrait will disappear. If this happens, you will have to blow the whistle following combat to dismiss and then summon the dog.

EVENT_TYPE_PARTY_MEMBER_FIRED is not getting routed to EDS. As a result, you should make sure you blow the whistle and remove the dog BEFORE the game removes the party, or you may break the game.  Here is a known list of offending locations (you should probably write these down):
Red Cliff:  When entering the fade to save the boy
Circle OF Magi: When entering the fade because of the sloth demon on the 4th floor
Orzamar : The provings.  Each round removes the party members
Denerim : At the pearl. If you sleep with anyone, the party is removed.
Denerim: If you win the lands meet and chose a 1 on 1 match with Logain."
6610152	"The Extra Dog Slot (EDS) Mod has detected a minor conflict with another mod.

EVENT_TYPE_COMMAND_PENDING or EVENT_TYPE_COMMAND_COMPLETE  is not getting routed to EDS. As a result, you should blow the whistle and remove the dog from the party before allowing Mages or Rogue-Rangers from summoning any creatures."
6610153	"The Extra Dog Slot (EDS) Mod has detected a minor conflict with another mod.

EVENT_TYPE_SUMMON_DIED is not getting routed to EDS. As a result, when summoned creatures die, the dog will not shift up to the uppermost summon slot. You will have to blow the whistle to re-summon the dog and shift the dog up manually.

EVENT_TYPE_COMMAND_PENDING or EVENT_TYPE_COMMAND_COMPLETE  is not getting routed to EDS. As a result, you should blow the whistle and remove the dog from the party before allowing Mages or Rogue-Rangers from summoning any creatures."
6610154	Dog Wistle
6610155	You found this whistle around the neck of your Mabari.
6610156	Endurance
6610157	"The mabari has undergone endurance and survival training, gaining a bonus to stamina."
6610158	Bond
6610159	"The mabari has formed a special bond with its master, gaining a bonus to mental resistance."
6610160	Frighten
6610161	"The mabari lets out a frightening howl, forcing nearby enemies to cower in fear unless they pass a mental resistance check."
6610162	Ferocious bite
6610163	"The mabari will jump on its target and bite its neck. If the target is a living creature, it will die instantly if of normal or lesser rank unless it passes a physical resistance check. Lieutenant-ranked enemies will suffer a critical hit, while boss-ranked enemies will take only standard damage. Additionally, all targets who can bleed will take additional damage over time.

Non-bleeding creatures will only take normal damage."
6610164	Meet Leliana at the hot springs
6610165	Artisan Wine Bath Soaps
6610166	"A bundle of artisan wine bath soaps from Orlais. Deep red in color, scented with berries and hints of oak.
This was a gift from Leliana."
6610167	Next Quickbar
6610168	Previous Quickbar
6610169	Pause
6610170	Advanced Quickbar
6610171	Advanced Tactics
6610172	Has low armor rating
6610173	Has medium armor rating
6610174	Has high armor rating
6610175	Has low or medium armor rating
6610176	Has medium or high armor rating
6610177	Rank is Critter
6610178	Rank is Normal
6610179	Rank is Elite
6610180	Rank is Boss
6610181	Rank is Elite Boss
6610182	At least 2 allies are alive
6610183	At least 3 allies are alive
6610184	At least 4 allies are alive
6610185	At short range
6610186	Between short and medium range
6610187	Between medium and long range
6610188	At least 2 allies have curable effects
6610189	At least 3 allies have curable effects
6610190	At least 4 allies have curable effects
6610191	Using melee attack
6610192	Using ranged attack
6610193	Using magic attack
6610194	Using melee or ranged attack
6610195	Using melee or magic attack
6610196	Using ranged or magic attack
6610197	Rank is Normal or lower
6610198	Rank is Elite or lower
6610199	Rank is Normal or higher
6610200	Rank is Elite or higher
6610201	Rank is Boss or higher
6610202	At least 2 allies are wounded (< 25%)
6610203	At least 3 allies are wounded (< 25%)
6610204	At least 4 allies are wounded (< 25%)
6610205	At least 2 allies are wounded (< 50%)
6610206	At least 3 allies are wounded (< 50%)
6610207	At least 4 allies are wounded (< 50%)
6610208	At least 2 allies are wounded (< 75%)
6610209	At least 3 allies are wounded (< 75%)
6610210	At least 4 allies are wounded (< 75%)
6610211	At least 2 allies are exhausted (< 25%)
6610212	At least 3 allies are exhausted (< 25%)
6610213	At least 4 allies are exhausted (< 25%)
6610214	At least 2 allies are exhausted (< 50%)
6610215	At least 3 allies are exhausted (< 50%)
6610216	At least 4 allies are exhausted (< 50%)
6610217	At least 2 allies are exhausted (< 75%)
6610218	At least 3 allies are exhausted (< 75%)
6610219	At least 4 allies are exhausted (< 75%)
6610220	Being attacked
6610221	Not being attacked by melee attacks
6610222	Not being attacked by ranged attacks
6610223	Not being attacked by magic attacks
6610224	Not being attacked by melee or ranged attacks
6610225	Not being attacked by melee or magic attacks
6610226	Not being attacked by ranged or magic attacks
6610227	Not being attacked
6610228	Exploration
6610229	Combat
6610230	Petrified / Frozen
6610231	Invulnerable
6610232	Affected by Weakness
6610233	Affected by Vulnerability Hex or Affliction Hex
6610234	Affected by Death Hex
6610235	Health < 100%
6610236	Health < 90%
6610237	Health < 80%
6610238	Health < 70%
6610239	Health < 60%
6610240	Health < 50%
6610241	Health < 40%
6610242	Health < 30%
6610243	Health < 20%
6610244	Health < 10%
6610245	Health >= 90%
6610246	Health >= 80%
6610247	Health >= 70%
6610248	Health >= 60%
6610249	Health >= 50%
6610250	Health >= 40%
6610251	Health >= 30%
6610252	Health >= 20%
6610253	Health >= 10%
6610254	Mana or stamina < 100%
6610255	Mana or stamina < 90%
6610256	Mana or stamina < 80%
6610257	Mana or stamina < 70%
6610258	Mana or stamina < 60%
6610259	Mana or stamina < 50%
6610260	Mana or stamina < 40%
6610261	Mana or stamina < 30%
6610262	Mana or stamina < 20%
6610263	Mana or stamina < 10%
6610264	Mana or stamina >= 90%
6610265	Mana or stamina >= 80%
6610266	Mana or stamina >= 70%
6610267	Mana or stamina >= 60%
6610268	Mana or stamina >= 50%
6610269	Mana or stamina >= 40%
6610270	Mana or stamina >= 30%
6610271	Mana or stamina >= 20%
6610272	Mana or stamina >= 10%
6610273	Using melee attack at flank
6610274	Is a summoned creature
6610275	Is accompanied by a summoned creature
6610276	Is not accompanied by a summoned creature
6610277	Has Curable Effects
6610278	Feared
6610279	Has debuff
6610280	Using ranged attacks at range
6610281	At range
6610282	Using attack type
6610283	Not being attacked by type of attack
6610284	Combat Status
6610285	Summoning
6610286	Target
6610287	Saved Enemy
6610288	Disarm traps
6610289	Pick locks
6610290	Switch to weapon set I
6610291	Switch to weapon set II
6610292	Pause
6610293	Behavior : Default
6610294	Behavior : Passive
6610295	Behavior : Aggressive
6610296	Behavior : Ranged
6610297	Behavior : Cautious
6610298	Behavior : Defensive
6610299	* Store as Saved Enemy
6610300	Possessed
6610301	Enable tactics for controlled characters.
6610302	Traitors
6610303	Your rogues allies attack enemies from behind.
6610304	Team Member
6610305	Nearest Target of Party Member
6610306	Attack - Hold Position
6610307	At medium range
6610308	At long range
6610309	At least X enemies at range
6610310	No enemies at medium range
6610311	At least 1 enemy at medium range
6610312	At least 2 enemies at medium range
6610313	At least 3 enemies at medium range
6610314	At least 4 enemies at medium range
6610315	At least 5 enemies at medium range
6610316	At least 6 enemies at medium range
6610317	In line of sight
6610318	Attack - Weapon Range
6610319	Melee Attack
6610320	Ranged Attack
6610321	Move at short
6610322	* Deactivate all stances
6610323	* Adjust ammo/cristal
6610324	* Unequip ammo
6610325	Break
6610326	Enemy AND
6610327	Has Resistance
6610328	Fire <75%
6610329	Fire < 50%
6610330	Fire < 33%
6610331	Cold < 75%
6610332	Cold < 50%
6610333	Cold < 33%
6610334	Spirit < 75%
6610335	Spirit < 50%
6610336	Spirit < 33%
6610337	Nature < 75%
6610338	Nature < 50%
6610339	Nature < 33%
6610340	Fire >= 75%
6610341	Fire >= 50%
6610342	Fire >= 33%
6610343	Cold >= 75%
6610344	Cold >= 50%
6610345	Cold >= 33%
6610346	Spirit >= 75%
6610347	Spirit >= 50%
6610348	Spirit >= 33%
6610349	Nature >= 75%
6610350	Nature >= 50%
6610351	Nature >= 33%
6610352	Move at medium
6610353	No enemies at short range
6610354	At least 1 enemy at short range
6610355	At least 2 enemies at short range
6610356	At least 3 enemies at short range
6610357	At least 4 enemies at short range
6610358	At least 5 enemies at short range
6610359	Further than short
6610360	Further than medium
6610361	Further than long
6610362	* Clear Secondary Target
6610363	Electricity < 75%
6610364	Electricity < 50%
6610365	Electricity < 33%
6610366	Electricity >= 75%
6610367	Electricity >= 50%
6610368	Electricity >= 33%
6610369	Switch Behavior: Range
6610370	Switch Behavior: Default
6610371	Switch Behavior: Aggresive
6610372	Switch Behavior: Passive
6610373	Switch Behavior: Cautious
6610374	Switch Behavior: Defensive
6610375	Disable Party Stances. Cancel Special Orders and Strategies
6610376	Change Personal Strategy
6610377	Change Party Strategy
6610378	Special Personal Strategy
6610379	Special Party Strategy
6610380	Standard Personal Strategy
6610381	Standard Party Strategy
6610382	Party Order: Execute Special Tactics
6610383	Party Order: Cancel Special Tactics Execution
6610384	Execute Special Tactic Order Issued
6610385	Mana or stamina < Max
6610386	Mana or stamina < Max - 25
6610387	Mana or stamina < Max - 50
6610388	Mana or stamina < Max - 75
6610389	Mana or stamina < Max - 100
6610390	Mana or stamina < Max - 125
6610391	Mana or stamina < Max - 150
6610392	Mana or stamina < Max - 175
6610393	Mana or stamina < Max - 200
6610394	Mana or stamina < Max - 225
6610395	Mana or stamina < Max - 250
6610396	Mana or stamina < Max - 275
6610397	Mana or stamina < Max - 300
6610398	Mana or stamina < Max - 325
6610399	Mana or stamina < Max - 350
6610400	Mana or stamina < Max - 375
6610401	Mana or stamina < Max - 400
6610402	Mana or stamina > 25
6610403	Mana or stamina > 50
6610404	Mana or stamina > 75
6610405	Mana or stamina > 100
6610406	Mana or stamina > 125
6610407	Mana or stamina > 150
6610408	Mana or stamina > 175
6610409	Mana or stamina > 200
6610410	Mana or stamina > 225
6610411	Mana or stamina > 250
6610412	Mana or stamina > 275
6610413	Mana or stamina > 300
6610414	Mana or stamina > 325
6610415	Mana or stamina > 350
6610416	Mana or stamina > 375
6610417	Mana or stamina > 400
6610418	No enemies at long range
6610419	At least 1 enemy at long range
6610420	At least 2 enemies at long range
6610421	At least 3 enemies at long range
6610422	At least 4 enemies at long range
6610423	At least 5 enemies at long range
6610424	No enemies at 2x short range
6610425	At least 1 enemy at 2 x short range
6610426	At least 2 enemies at 2 x short range
6610427	At least 3 enemies at 2 x short range
6610428	At least 4 enemies at 2 x short range
6610429	At least 5 enemies at 2 x short range
6610430	No enemies at 2x medium range
6610431	At least 1 enemy at 2 x medium range
6610432	At least 2 enemies at 2 x medium range
6610433	At least 3 enemies at 2 x medium range
6610434	At least 4 enemies at 2 x medium range
6610435	At least 5 enemies at 2 x medium range
6610436	No enemies at bow range
6610437	At least 1 enemy at bow range
6610438	At least 2 enemies at bow range
6610439	At least 3 enemies at bow range
6610440	At least 4 enemies at bow range
6610441	At least 5 enemies at bow range
6610442	Has Enchanted Weapon
6610443	Dwarf
6610444	Elf
6610445	Human
6610446	Qunari
6610447	Animal
6610448	Beast
6610449	Darkspawn
6610450	Dragon
6610451	Golem
6610452	Spirit
6610453	Undead
6610454	Warrior
6610455	Mage
6610456	Rogue
6610457	Male
6610458	Female
6610459	Race
6610460	Class
6610461	Gender
6610462	Party
6610463	BooleanVar
6610464	* Boolean [ 1 ] = Cond.Result
6610465	* Boolean [ 2 ] = Cond.Result
6610466	* Boolean [ 1 ] = NOT Cond.Result
6610467	* Boolean [ 2 ] = NOT Cond.Result
6610468	* Boolean [ 1 ] = Cond.Result AND Boolean [ 1 ]
6610469	* Boolean [ 2 ] = Cond.Result AND Boolean [ 2 ]
6610470	* Boolean [ 1 ] = Cond.Result OR Boolean [ 1 ]
6610471	* Boolean [ 2 ] = Cond.Result OR Boolean [ 2 ]
6610472	AND
6610473	OR
6610474	NOT
6610475	Boolean [ 1 ]
6610476	Boolean [ 2 ]
6610477	AND Boolean [ 1 ]
6610478	AND Boolean [ 2 ]
6610479	OR Boolean [ 1 ]
6610480	OR Boolean [ 2 ]
6610481	NOT Boolean [ 1 ]
6610482	NOT Boolean [ 2 ]
6610483	VALUE
6610484	Logic
6610485	Boolean [ 1 ] AND Boolean [ 2 ]
6610486	Boolean [ 1 ] OR Boolean [ 2 ]
6610487	No enemies at short range of party
6610488	At least 1 enemy at short range of party
6610489	At least 2 enemies at short range of party
6610490	At least 3 enemies at short range of party
6610491	At least 4 enemies at short range of party
6610492	At least 5 enemies at short range of party
6610493	No enemies at medium range of party
6610494	At least 1 enemy at medium range of party
6610495	At least 2 enemies at medium range of party
6610496	At least 3 enemies at medium range of party
6610497	At least 4 enemies at medium range of party
6610498	At least 5 enemies at medium range of party
6610499	No enemies at long range of party
6610500	At least 1 enemy at long range of party
6610501	At least 2 enemies at long range of party
6610502	At least 3 enemies at long range of party
6610503	At least 4 enemies at long range of party
6610504	At least 5 enemies at long range of party
6610505	No enemies at  2 x short range of party
6610506	At least 1 enemy at  2 x short range of party
6610507	At least 2 enemies at  2 x short range of party
6610508	At least 3 enemies at  2 x short range of party
6610509	At least 4 enemies at  2 x short range of party
6610510	At least 5 enemies at  2 x short range of party
6610511	No enemies at  2 x medium range of party
6610512	At least 1 enemy at  2 x medium range of party
6610513	At least 2 enemies at  2 x medium range of party
6610514	At least 3 enemies at  2 x medium range of party
6610515	At least 4 enemies at  2 x medium range of party
6610516	At least 5 enemies at  2 x medium range of party
6610517	No enemies at bow range of party
6610518	At least 1 enemy at  bow range of party
6610519	At least 2 enemies at bow range of party
6610520	At least 3 enemies at  bow range of party
6610521	At least 4 enemies at  bow range of party
6610522	At least 5 enemies at  bow range of party
6610523	At least X enemies at range of party
6610524	* Boolean [ 1 ] = NOT Cond.Result AND Boolean [ 1 ]
6610525	* Boolean [ 2 ] = NOT Cond.Result AND Boolean [ 2 ]
6610526	* Boolean [ 1 ] = NOT Cond.Result OR Boolean [ 1 ]
6610527	* Boolean [ 2 ] = NOT Cond.Result OR Boolean [ 2 ]
6610528	Behaviors
6610529	Orders and Strategies
6610530	Others
6610531	Combat Start
6610532	Customize Behavior: Avoid AOE
6610533	Customize Behavior: Move to X
6610534	Set as Target
6610535	* Set as Target
6610536	MultiCondition Enemy
6610537	* Add condition
6610538	At 2 x short range
6610539	At 2 x medium range
6610540	At bow range
6610541	Further than 2 x short 
6610542	Further than 2 x medium
6610543	Further than bow
6610544	Can attack
6610545	Not Polymorphed
6610546	Not Charmed
6610547	Not Paralyzed
6610548	Not Stuned
6610549	Not Sleeping
6610550	Not Knockdown
6610551	Not Rooted
6610552	Not Dazed
6610553	Not Slowed
6610554	Not Grabbed
6610555	Not Grabbing
6610556	Not Berserk
6610557	Not Stealthed
6610558	Not Dead
6610559	Not Immobilized
6610560	Not Movement Impaired
6610561	Not Petrified / Frozen
6610562	Not Invulnerable
6610563	Not Feared
6610564	Not AI status
6610565	Rogue - Feign Death
6610566	Rogue (DAA) - Ghost
6610567	Rogue (DAA) - Weak Points
6610568	Warrior - Threaten
6610569	Warrior - Precise Striking
6610570	Warrior - Perfect Striking 
6610571	Shale - Pulverizing Blows
6610572	Shale - Stoneheart
6610573	Shale - Rock Mastery
6610574	Shale - Stone Aura
6610575	Dual Weapon - Dual Striking
6610576	Dual Weapon - Momentum
6610577	Archery - Aim
6610578	Archery - Defensive Fire
6610579	Archery - Rapid Shot
6610580	Archery - Suppressing Fire
6610581	Archery (DAA) - Accuracy
6610582	Archery (DAA) - Arrow Time
6610583	Shield - Shield Defense
6610584	Shield - Shield Wall
6610585	Shield - Shield Cover
6610586	Shield (DAA) - Juggernaut
6610587	Shield (DAA) - Carapace
6610588	Shield (DAA) - Air of Insolence
6610589	Two-Handed - Indomitable
6610590	Two-Handed - Powerful Swings
6610591	Two-Handed (DAA) - Two-Handed Impact
6610592	Two-Handed (DAA) - Reaving Storm
6610593	Arcane - Arcane Shield
6610594	Arcane (DAA) - Elemental Mastery
6610595	Arcane (DAA) - Repulsion Field
6610596	Arcane (DAA) - Invigorate
6610597	Arcane (DAA) - Arcane Field
6610598	Arcane (DAA) - Mystical Negation
6610599	Primal - Rock Armor
6610600	Creation - Spell Wisp
6610601	Creation - Spellbloom
6610602	Spirit - Spell Shield
6610603	Spirit - Spell Might
6610604	Spirit - Death Syphon
6610605	Spirit - Animate Dead
6610606	Entropy - Miasma
6610607	Entropy - Death Magic
6610608	Bard - Song of Valor
6610609	Bard - Song of Courage
6610610	Bard - Captivating Song
6610611	Duelist - Dueling
6610612	Legionnaire Scout - Strength of Stone
6610613	Legionnaire Scout - Endure Hardship
6610614	Shadow - Shadow Form
6610615	Berserker - Berserk
6610616	Reaver - Aura of Pain
6610617	Reaver - Blood Frenzy
6610618	Champion - Rally
6610619	Guardian (DAA) - Fortifying Presence
6610620	Guardian (DAA) - Aura of the Stalwart Defender
6610621	Spirit Warrior (DAA) - Beyond the Veil
6610622	Arcane Warrior - Combat Magic
6610623	Arcane Warrior - Shimmering Shield
6610624	Blood Mage - Blood Magic
6610625	Battlemage (DAA) - Draining Aura
6610626	Battlemage (DAA) - Elemental Chaos
6610627	Keeper (DAA) - One With Nature
6610628	Power of Blood - Dark Sustenance
6610629	Power of Blood - Bloody Grasp
6610630	Wynne - Vessel of the Spirit
6610631	Creation - Rejuvenate
6610632	Creation - Regeneration
6610633	Creation - Mass Rejuvenation
6610634	Creation - Heroic Offense
6610635	Creation - Heroic Aura
6610636	Creation - Heroic Defense
6610637	Creation - Haste
6610638	Creation - Glyph of Warding
6610639	Spirit - Antimagic Ward
6610640	Spirit Healer - Lifeward
6610641	Spirit Healer - Cleansing Aura
6610642	Affected by Misdirection Hex
6610643	Affected by Curse of Mortality
6610644	Affected by Waking Nightmare
6610645	Affected by Force Field
6610646	Affected by Crushing Prison
6610647	Affected by Walking Bomb or Virulent Walking Bomb
6610648	Affected by Stinging Swarm
6610649	Affected by Blood Control
6610650	Affected by debuff worth to dispell
6610651	Boolean [ 1 ] AND Boolean [ 2 ]
6610652	Boolean [ 1 ] AND NOT Boolean [ 2 ]
6610653	NOT Boolean [ 1 ] AND Boolean [ 2 ]
6610654	Not Boolean [ 1 ] AND NOT Boolean [ 2 ]
6610655	Boolean [ 1 ] OR Boolean [ 2 ]
6610656	Boolean [ 1 ] OR NOT Boolean [ 2 ]
6610657	NOT Boolean [ 1 ] OR Boolean [ 2 ]
6610658	NOT Boolean [ 1 ] OR NOT Boolean [ 2 ]
6610659	Saved Friend
6610660	* Store as Saved Friend
6610661	Spellcaster
6610662	Customize Default Behavior
6610663	Customize Default Behavior: Avoid AOE
6610664	Customize Default Behavior: Attack Back
6610665	Customize Default Behavior: Chase Enemy
6610666	Customize Default Behavior: Attack on Combat Start
6610667	Customize Default Behavior: Weapon
6610668	Customize Default Behavior: Avoid Nearby Enemies
6610669	Customize Default Behavior: Avoid Melee
6610670	Customize Default Behavior: Default Attack
6610671	Behavior Status
6610672	Magic  < 75
6610673	Magic  < 50
6610674	Magic  < 33
6610675	Magic  >= 75
6610676	Magic  >= 50
6610677	Magic  >= 33
6610678	Immune - Knockdown
6610679	Immune - Stun
6610680	Immune - Disease
6610681	Immune - Daze
6610682	Immune - Sleep
6610683	Immune - Charm
6610684	Immune - Confusion
6610685	Immune - Fear
6610686	Immune - Root
6610687	Immune - Slip
6610688	Not Immune - Knockdown
6610689	Not Immune - Stun
6610690	Not Immune - Disease
6610691	Not Immune - Daze
6610692	Not Immune - Sleep
6610693	Not Immune - Charm
6610694	Not Immune - Confusion
6610695	Not Immune - Fear
6610696	Not Immune - Root
6610697	Not Immune - Slip
6610698	Teammate
6610699	Team Member
6610700	Party Member
6610701	Nearest Target of Ally
6610702	Nearest Target of Teammate
6610703	Nearest Target of Team Member
6610704	Nearest Target of Party Member
6610705	Sort By
6610706	Self First
6610707	Current Target First
6610708	Highest Health
6610709	Lowest Health
6610710	Highest Rank
6610711	Lowest Rank
6610712	Highest Armor
6610713	Lowest Armor
6610714	Highest Mana/Stamina
6610715	Lowest Mana/Stamina
6610716	MultiCondition Friend
6610717	Sorting preferences Friend
6610718	Prefer Self
6610719	Prefer Follower
6610720	Prefer Hero
6610721	Prefer Controlled
6610722	Exclude Self
6610723	Exclude Follower
6610724	Exclude Hero
6610725	Exclude Controlled
6610726	Exclude Summoned
6610727	Include Dead
6610728	CUT
6610729	CUT
6610730	CUT
6610731	CUT
6610732	CUT
6610733	Prefer Target of Self
6610734	Prefer Target of Follower
6610735	Prefer Target of Hero
6610736	Prefer Target of Controlled
6610737	Exclude Target of Self
6610738	Exclude Target of Follower
6610739	Exclude Target of Hero
6610740	Exclude Target of Controlled
6610741	Include Dead 
6610742	Include Sleeped/Rooted
6610743	CUT
6610744	CUT
6610745	CUT
6610746	CUT
6610747	CUT
6610748	Is valid for ability
6610749	MultiCondition Settings
6610750	Sorting preferences Enemy
6610751	Surrounded by at least five enemies
6610752	Surrounded by at least six enemies
6610753	Has Fire Weapon
6610754	Has Cold Weapon
6610755	Has Telekinetic Weapon
6610756	At least two enemy is alive
6610757	At least four enemies are alive
6610758	At least six enemies are alive
6610759	"Clustered with same group, 1+"
6610760	"Clustered with same group, 2+"
6610761	"Clustered with same group, 3+"
6610762	"Clustered with same group, 4+"
6610763	"Clustered with same group, 5+"
6610764	"Clustered with same group, 6+"
6610765	Race
6610766	Confused
6610767	Affected by spell
6610768	Affected by talent
6610769	Even More Advanced Tactics
6610770	This add-in introduces huge improvements to Tactic System. It is based on Advanced Tactic by anakin55. For more details referer to manual.
6610771	Default
6610772	[> Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: NO > Switch to Ranged Weapon: NO > Ranged Attack: Enemy in Line of Sight (prefer current) > Melee Attack: Enemy within Medium range of any TeamMember (prefer current)]
6610773	Passive
6610774	Passive neither switches weapon nor attacks enemies. It is intended for characters that are fully controlled by TacticTable. [> Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: NO > Switch to Ranged Weapon: NO > Ranged Attack: not at all > Melee Attack: not at all]
6610775	Aggresive
6610776	Aggresive is intended for characters that charge toward enemies. Aggresive attacks and looks for enemies on much greater area than Default. [> Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: NO > Switch to Ranged Weapon: NO > Ranged Attack: Enemy in Line of Sight (prefer current) > Melee Attack: Enemy within 2xMedium range of any TeamMember (prefer current)]
6610777	Ranged
6610778	"Ranged is intended for archers. It strongly prefers ranged weapon, tries to avoid Nearby Enemies and doesn't attack in melee. [> Avoid Nearby Enemies: YES > Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: NO > Switch to Ranged Weapon: when no Enemies within Short range of Self > Ranged Attack: Enemy in Line of Sight (prefer current) > Melee Attack: not at all]"
6610779	Cautious
6610780	Cautious is intended for support characters. Attack on current target is continued but it doesn't choose a new one. Cautious doesn't want to draw opponents attention. [> Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: NO > Switch to Ranged Weapon: NO > Ranged Attack: Current Attack Target if in Line of Sight > Melee Attack: Current Attack Target if within 2xShort range of Self]
6610781	Defensive
6610782	Defensive prefers to attack from distance but he doesn't escape from enemies. Defensive switches to melee and engages opponents if they are close enough. [> Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: when an Enemy within 2xShort range of Self > Switch to Ranged Weapon: when no Enemies within Medium range of Self > Ranged Attack: Enemy in Line of Sight (prefer current) > Melee Attack: Enemy within Medium range of Self (prefer current)]
6610783	Protective
6610784	Protective is intended for fighters that use bow but melee weapon is their primary weapon of choice. This behavior switches to bow when there is no enemies in proximity so fighter can weaken opponents before clashing in melee. Fighter immediately switches to melee and attacks any enemy if he come too close to any TeamMember. This way Protective can efficiently protect Support characters. [> Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: when an Enemy within 2xShort range of any TeamMember > Switch to Ranged Weapon: when no Enemies within Medium range of all TeamMembers > Ranged Attack: Enemy in Line of Sight (prefer current) > Melee Attack: Enemy within Medium range of any TeamMember (prefer current)]
6610785	Templar
6610786	Templar is like Default behavior but has Avoid AoE feature disabled. It is intended for characters with high magic/elemental resistance and/or using Indomitable/ShieldWall. [> Avoid AOE: NO  > Switch to Melee Weapon: NO > Switch to Ranged Weapon: NO > Ranged Attack: Enemy in Line of Sight (prefer current) > Melee Attack: Enemy within Medium range of any TeamMember (prefer current)]
6610787	Default Stationary
6610788	[> Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: NO > Switch to Ranged Weapon: NO > Ranged Attack: Enemy in Line of Sight (prefer current) > Melee Attack: Enemy within Medium range of any TeamMember (prefer current)]
6610789	Passive Stationary
6610790	Passive neither switches weapon nor attacks enemies. It is intended for characters that are fully controlled by TacticTable. [> Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: NO > Switch to Ranged Weapon: NO > Ranged Attack: not at all > Melee Attack: not at all]
6610791	Aggresive Stationary
6610792	Aggresive is intended for characters that charge toward enemies. Aggresive attacks and looks for enemies on much greater area than Default. [> Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: NO > Switch to Ranged Weapon: NO > Ranged Attack: Enemy in Line of Sight (prefer current) > Melee Attack: Enemy within 2xMedium range of any TeamMember (prefer current)]
6610793	Ranged Stationary
6610794	"Ranged is intended for archers. It strongly prefers ranged weapon, tries to avoid Nearby Enemies and doesn't attack in melee. [> Avoid Nearby Enemies: YES > Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: NO > Switch to Ranged Weapon: when no Enemies within Short range of Self > Ranged Attack: Enemy in Line of Sight (prefer current) > Melee Attack: not at all]"
6610795	Cautious Stationary
6610796	Cautious is intended for support characters. Attack on current target is continued but it doesn't choose a new one. Cautious doesn't want to draw opponents attention. [> Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: NO > Switch to Ranged Weapon: NO > Ranged Attack: Current Attack Target if in Line of Sight > Melee Attack: Current Attack Target if within 2xShort range of Self]
6610797	Defensive Stationary
6610798	Defensive prefers to attack from distance but he doesn't escape from enemies. Defensive switches to melee and engages opponents if they are close enough. [> Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: when an Enemy within 2xShort range of Self > Switch to Ranged Weapon: when no Enemies within Medium range of Self > Ranged Attack: Enemy in Line of Sight (prefer current) > Melee Attack: Enemy within Medium range of Self (prefer current)]
6610799	Protective Stationary
6610800	Protective is intended for fighters that use bow but melee weapon is their primary weapon of choice. This behavior switches to bow when there is no enemies in proximity so fighter can weaken opponents before clashing in melee. Fighter immediately switches to melee and attacks any enemy if he come too close to any TeamMember. This way Protective can efficiently protect Support characters. [> Avoid AOE: YES > Switch to Melee Weapon: when an Enemy within 2xShort range of any TeamMember > Switch to Ranged Weapon: when no Enemies within Medium range of all TeamMembers > Ranged Attack: Enemy in Line of Sight (prefer current) > Melee Attack: Enemy within Medium range of any TeamMember (prefer current)]
6610801	Templar Stationary
6610802	Templar is like Default behavior but has Avoid AoE feature disabled. It is intended for characters with high magic/elemental resistance and/or using Indomitable/ShieldWall. [> Avoid AOE: NO  > Switch to Melee Weapon: NO > Switch to Ranged Weapon: NO > Ranged Attack: Enemy in Line of Sight (prefer current) > Melee Attack: Enemy within Medium range of any TeamMember (prefer current)]
6610803	Required: Female
6610804	Required: Male
6610805	Ring of Survival
6610806	"This plain looking ring was once the posession of a Telvinter mage who fell during the First Blight and subsequently found and worn by a Chasind chief during their occupation of Ostagar. How it came to be lost again is a mystery, but it's power has remain undimished over the ages."
6610807	Ivory Tower Bulwark
6610808	"This strange armour looks like a mage robe combined with plate armour. It was created for the Arcane Warrior guards who defended the elven magical towers. Its surface is unbearable cold to the human touch, but warm and pleasant to elven hands. Its appeling beauty is a reminder of what elves have lost and what they could again aspire to again."
6610809	Ivory Tower Spire
6610810	Elegant helmet of elven design that once belonged to a warmage guard. Its silvery white surface glitters under moonlight.
6610811	Ivory Tower Handguards
6610812	"This pair of gloves may look heavy, but to an Arcane warrior they are incredibly light and flexible"
6610813	Ivory Tower Foundation
6610814	"Silvery white boots, covered in vine scrollwork and long forgotten runes"
6610815	Blossom of Nightfall
6610816	"Velvet blue and covered in stars and vines, as its sister longsword, this dagger radiates a strong arcane aura."
6610817	Dusk Fluorescence
6610818	The surface of this longsword is dark blue in colour with etching of a starry sky above vines and flowers.
6610819	Wall of Twilight
6610820	The strange metal of this shield not only deflects incoming attacks it also reflects its surroundings like a real mirror.
6610821	Crescent Talons
6610822	Light boots covered in vines and with and ornate toecap in the form of a bird of preys talons. 
6610823	Feathers of Dusk
6610824	"Beautiful and ornate this robe was custom made for an elven archmage that lived in Halamshiral before the dark clouds of  human  intolerance thickened above the Dales. It is made from the fabric akin to leather by the look of it, but to the touch it is astonishingly close to the brocade.  Adorned by the blue jewels that are cased in unknown silvery metal. The surface is covered in floral elements with the embroidery in satin-stitch of the owl's head that is clearly seen on robes front hem."
6610825	Claws of Twilight
6610826	"Adorned with embroidery of feathers, floral patterns and strange, long forgotten runes this pair of delicate gloves as clearly made for ancient elven mage whose name was lost long ago."
6610827	Nights Eyes
6610828	"This hood is made from the strange material that is similar to the leather and brocade at the same time. Patterns on the surface are done in a manner of exotic plants and strange swirls, but the main element is an owl's head that is embroidered in silk on the temple of the hood. This piece of mage armor is clearly of elven work that was created many centuries ago. It's really a miracle that it still look and fill like it have been made just now and especially for you."
6610829	Lance of Moonlight
6610830	This ornate stave looks newly done but feel like a truly ancient item. Two black dragons are holding a ball of clear blue color. If you look at it long enough you will see the summer night sky that full of stars.
6610831	Sundown Boots
6610832	"These boots, from the sundown hunter ranger equipment, are crafted from some form of extremely tough, but flexible, leatherand enscribed with feather designs and patterns. On inspection they appear to be bright in colour but when worn they seem to deflect the eye."
6610833	Sundown Chestpiece
6610834	"This chest armour, from the sundown hunter ranger equipment, is crafted from some form of extremely tough, but flexible, leather and enscribed with feather designs and patterns."
6610835	Sundown Gloves
6610836	"These gloves, like the rest of the sundown hunter ranger equipment, is crafted from some form of extremely tough, but flexible, leather and enscribed with feather designs and patterns."
6610837	Sundown Helmet
6610838	"This helmet, like the rest of the sundown hunter ranger equipment, is crafted from some form of extremely tough, but flexible, leather and enscribed with feather designs and patterns."
6610839	Sundown Longbow
6610840	"This elegant bow of elven craft seems not to have been shaped out of wood, instead it looks to have been grown into the shape somehow. It is decorated with gems, gold and strips of wonderfully manufactured leather."
6610841	Sunrise
6610842	Sunset
6610843	Daybreak
6610844	Nightfall
6610845	Phoenix Long Eye
6610846	This elegant whitewood longbow is warm to the touch and seems to transfer that heat to it's arrows as they have a chance of setting their targets on fire.
6610847	Phoenix-Matriarch Long Eye
6610848	This elegant dragonthorn longbow is a more powerful version of the whitewood bow and is warm to the touch and seems to transfer that heat to it's arrows as they have a chance of setting their targets on fire.
6610849	Phoenix Eye
6610850	This elegant whitewood shortbow is warm to the touch and seems to transfer that heat to it's arrows as they have a chance of setting their targets on fire.
6610851	Phoenix-Matriarch Eye
6610852	This elegant dragonthorn shortbow is a more powerful version of the whitewood bow and is warm to the touch and seems to transfer that heat to it's arrows as they have a chance of setting their targets on fire.
6610853	Phoenix Claw Mig
6610854	This finely crafted viridium dagger has a handle that seems to mould into the wielders hand and feels like a part of the users hand making it easier to find weakspots. It has a uniquely folded edge that seems to be particularly aggravating to spellusers.
6610855	Phoenix-Matriarch Claw Mig
6610856	This finely crafted dragonbone dagger has a handle that seems to mould into the wielders hand and feels like a part of the users hand making it easier to find weakspots. It has a uniquely folded edge that seems to be particularly aggravating to spellusers.
6610857	Phoenix Claw Hidar
6610858	This finely crafted viridium dagger has a handle that seems to mould into the wielders hand and feels like a part of the users hand making it easier to find weakspots. It has a uniquely crafted edge that seems to disorient targets.
6610859	Phoenix-Matriarch Claw Hidar
6610860	This finely crafted dragonbone dagger has a handle that seems to mould into the wielders hand and feels like a part of the users hand making it easier to find weakspots. It has a uniquely crafted edge that seems to disorient targets.
6610861	Phoenix Flash
6610862	"These arrows are perfectly balanced, and will fly more swiftly than the common arrow, taking a target by surprise stunning them briefly.
The arrows seem to want to jump into place in the Phoenix bows."
6610863	Phoenix Disruptor
6610864	"These arrows are coated in a mildly poisonous powder. On impact, the powder surrounds the target, burning their skin and eyes and causing them to lose concentration.
The arrows seem to want to jump into place in the Phoenix bows."
6610865	Phoenix Thunder
6610866	"These arrows hit with such force that they have been known to knock targets off their feet.
The arrows seem to want to jump into place in the Phoenix bows."
6610867	Phoenix Scout Armour
6610868	"This armour is light and unemcumbering, seeming to flex and support your movements making them easier and less tiring."
6610869	Phoenix Scout Boots
6610870	"These light boots grip your feet tightly without any pinching, allowing you to shift your feet more quickly during evasive manoeuvers. This is fairly obvious to enemies who often look for easier targets."
6610871	Phoenix Scout Gloves
6610872	These light gloves provide a much securer grip on your weapons making them more effective ate hitting their targets. They are particularly effective when used with a bow.
6610873	Phoenix Battlemaid Helmet
6610874	This medium helmet seems to enhance your mental faculties somehow alongside providing additionl protection.
6610875	Phoenix Battlemaid Armour
6610876	"This medium armour is unemcumbering, seeming to flex and support your movements making them easier and less tiring."
6610877	Phoenix Battlemaid Boots
6610878	"These medium boots grip your feet tightly without any pinching, allowing you to shift your feet more quickly during evasive manoeuvers. This is fairly obvious to enemies who often look for easier targets."
6610879	Phoenix Battlemaid Gloves
6610880	These medium gloves provide a much securer grip on your weapons making them more effective ate hitting their targets. They are particularly effective when used with a bow.
6610881	Phoenix Matriarch Gloves
6610882	"These heavy gloves are extremely flexible, provided a much securer grip on your weapons making them more effective ate hitting their targets. They are particularly effective when used with a bow."
6610883	Phoenix Matriarch Armour
6610884	"This heavy armour feels as though it is much lighter than it actually is, seeming to flex and support your movements making them easier and less tiring."
6610885	Phoenix Matriarch Boots
6610886	"These boots, though of heavy material, allow you to shift your feet more quickly during evasive manoeuvers. This is fairly obvious to enemies who often look for easier targets."
6610887	Garahel's Boots
6610888	"Worn by the legendary grey warden Garahel during the battle of Ayesleigh, where he slew the archdemon Andoral and ended the fourth blight. This armour is a masterpiece crafted by the best grey warden blacksmiths and enchanted to enhance it's wearer. Althoughh it's owner has perished, the armour still survives to continue the fight."
6610889	Garahel's Armour
6610890	"Worn by the legendary grey warden Garahel during the battle of Ayesleigh, where he slew the archdemon Andoral and ended the fourth blight. This armour is a masterpiece crafted by the best grey warden blacksmiths and enchanted to enhance it's wearer. Althoughh it's owner has perished, the armour still survives to continue the fight."
6610891	Garahel's Gauntlets
6610892	"Worn by the legendary grey warden Garahel during the battle of Ayesleigh, where he slew the archdemon Andoral and ended the fourth blight. This armour is a masterpiece crafted by the best grey warden blacksmiths and enchanted to enhance it's wearer. Althoughh it's owner has perished, the armour still survives to continue the fight."
6610893	Garahel's Fury
6610894	"Wielded by the legendary grey warden Garahel during the battle of Ayesleigh, where he slew the archdemon Andoral and ended the fourth blight. This weapon is a masterpiece crafted by the best grey warden blacksmiths and enchanted to enhance it's wearer. Althoughh it's owner has perished, the sword still survives to continue the fight."
6610895	Garahel's Vigilance
6610896	"Wielded by the legendary grey warden Garahel during the battle of Ayesleigh, where he slew the archdemon Andoral and ended the fourth blight. This weapon is a masterpiece crafted by the best grey warden blacksmiths and enchanted to enhance it's wearer. Althoughh it's owner has perished, the sword still survives to continue the fight."
89120084	Spider Cave
89120086	Cave Exit
89120087	Queen Spider
89120090	"You have killed some spiders guarding a cluster of cocoons. One of the cocoons seems to be moving slightly, and making a muffled noise."
89120091	You have killed all the spiders and found Arbither's father's body.
89120093	"You have returned Arbither's father's possessions to her. She was especially pleased to receive his twin swords.

Once she has had time to bury her father, she asks that you come to see her in Lothering Chantry as she has need of further help."
89120095	You have recovered an amulet and a pair of very smart swords from Ser Nathan's body.
89120096	"Ser Arbither has rewarded you for rescuing her, but you have declined to help her recover her father's body."
89120097	You have stolen Ser Arbither's swords from her.
89120099	You have rescued Ser Arbither Cora of Lothering from a spider's cocoon.
89120100	"You have killed Ser Arbither Cora, along with many of the Templars who were guarding refugees in Lothering.

On the plus side, you have gained a very nice pair of swords."
89120102	You have stolen Ser Arbither's swords from her - she is bitterly angry but unable to do anything about it.
89120104	Spiders & Knives
89120105	Spider Cave
89120107	"Ser Arbither Cora, knight of Lothering, is missing. She was last seen heading toward Spider Cave, north of Lothering.

Ser Arbither is a well-respected knight, whose like is needful in these troubled times. Her friends are offering a reward for word of her whereabouts, for her rescue, or for recovery of her body."
89120108	"<emp>Rescue Ser Arbither Cora</emp>

You read on the job board about a Lothering knight who has gone missing. A reward will be paid to anyone who finds/rescues her."
89120109	"<emp>Find Ser Arbither's Father</emp>

You have rescued Ser Arbither from a spider's cocoon. She is going to the Chantry, but has asked you to find her father's body and effects."
89120110	Ser Arbither has rewarded you for rescuing her from the spiders.
89120111	"<emp>Too Late To Rescue Ser Arbither Cora</emp>

With the destruction of Lothering, the fate of Ser Arbither Cora remains a mystery."
89120112	Rescue Ser Arbither
89120113	"A request from Ser Arbither Cora, knight of Lothering:

Darkspawn have overrun Knife Edge Manor, my family home. In the absence of my father, who is missing, presumed dead, I call for the assistance of a hero who will help me retake the manor, and rescue certain artefacts held within.

If you are that hero, meet me in Lothering Chantry to plan our attack.

This is a dangerous mission, and the reward will be commensurate."
89120114	"<emp>Retake Knife Edge</emp>

You read on the job board about a Lothering knight who seeks help in retaking her manor from the darkspawn."
89120115	"<emp>Speak to Ser Arbither cora</emp>

You have helped Ser Arbither retake her manor, and should speak to her for your reward."
89120116	Ser Arbither Cora has rewarded you for your help in retaking her manor.
89120117	"<emp>Too Late To Retake Knife Edge</emp>

With the destruction of Lothering, it seems unlikely that you will be able to contact Ser Arbither Cora."
89120118	"You have arrived at Knife Edge, Ser Arbither Cora's manor."
89120119	Retake Knife Edge
89120120	Cave Exit
89120122	Cocooned Body
89120124	Ser Nathan Cora
89120125	"Shrouded in spider silk, this dessicated corpse looks almost lifelike, but somehow ... wrong!"
89120126	Ser Nathan's Amulet
89120127	This amulet is intricately carved with a coat of arms.
89120128	Ser Arbither Cora
89120129	"Very aristocratic, maybe a little snooty, but she looks tough, with a slightly wild glint in her eyes."
89120130	"<desc>This cocoon appears to be moving slightly, and there are muffled noises coming from it</desc>"
89120131	<desc>A figure falls out of the cocoon</desc>
89120132	<desc>After a moment the movement and noises die down</desc>
89120133	<desc>The movement and noises intensify</desc>
89120134	<desc>This cocoon is now empty</desc>
89120135	<act>Cut the cocoon open</act>
89120137	<desc>Silently watch the cocoon</desc>
89120138	Is there anyone in there?
89120139	<desc>Leave the cocoon alone</desc>
89120141	The Crane
89120143	The Crow
89120145	"I say, I am most awfully grateful. It was dashed unpleasant in there."
89120146	"I'm Arbither Cora, don't you know, but you can call me 'Knives' - most folk do."
89120147	Are you game to finish the job? Of course you are! My Father's remains are somewhere further in.
89120148	"So kill the rest of those leggy blighters for me, and bring me his effects, and I'll see it's worth your while."
89120149	"Got to get to the Chantry now, before these bally eggs hatch. Meet me there. Maker speed!"
89120150	"Wonderful, you made it! Did you manage to find my poor father?"
89120151	I'm grateful to you. And have you brought me his things?
89120152	Excellent fellow! You deserve your reward for that.
89120153	Now the spiders are gone I can arrange to have my father's body recovered.
89120154	"But come back later, I've got a job that'll be just up your street. Maker's blessings!"
89120155	Good chap! I'll wait for you here.
89120156	"Oh! Very well, here is your reward. If you change your mind, I'll be here for a  while."
89120157	Jolly good show! We showed those filthy darkspawn!
89120158	"I said you'd be rewarded, and so you shall."
89120159	"You helped me get my father's swords, here's an item of my mother's that I'm sure will be of use."
89120160	"The labourer is worthy of his hire,  as they say."
89120161	"Maker willing, this place should be somewhere for the templars to fall back to when Lothering falls."
89120162	"This place is bally filthy! I must get some servants in, those elves are so good at cleaning!"
89120163	"Hail, stout hero! Are you ready to help retake Knife Edge from the filthy darkspawn?"
89120164	Good show! Let us be on our way.
89120165	Good day to you.
89120171	"Yes, the spiders had killed him. They're dead now."
89120172	I found his medallion and swords for you.
89120176	"No, I had to come out for supplies. I'll return shortly."
89120178	No. I've rescued you and that's enough.
89120186	I am indeed.
89120204	"<desc>Shrouded in spider silk, this dessicated corpse looks almost lifelike, but somehow ... wrong!</desc>"
89120206	Knife Edge
89120208	Knife Edge
89120209	"Ser Arbither Cora's home, near the road to Redcliffe"
89120214	The Crane
89120216	The Crow
89120218	Knotwood Staff
89120219	This gnarled staff's origin can be traced back to the Knotwood Hills. No doubt it once belonged to a hangman's tree or worse; a darkspawn scratching pole!
89120220	Thunderer
89120221	The unusual design of this heavy one-handed weapon appears to be of foreign origin. The air around the head of the weapon crackles with electrical energy.
89120222	HjorrMikill
89120223	"HjorMikill' means GreatSword in an ancient language. 
Protected by the mountains and snow, this sword was probably forged for a King when the elders were young, to protect in troubled times."
89120224	Dagger of Ashyera's Followers
89120225	These daggers - though they're scarce in Ferelden - are commonly wielded by a sect within a petty state of the Free Marches.
89120228	"<emp>Meet Ser Arbither In The Chantry</emp>

You have rescued Ser Arbither from a spider's cocoon, and found her father's body and effects. Meet her in the Chantry for your reward."
89120230	"I do hope you'll pop in when we're ship-shape again, old chap. I'll put a chest in the Hunter's Room for your use."
89120233	"You have accompanied Ser Arbither Cora to Knife Edge, her manor."
89120234	You have succeeded in helping Ser Arbither Cora recapture her manor from the darkspawn.
89120235	"Your quest to regain Knife Edge for Ser Arbither Cora is complete. She has indicated that you are welcome to return at any time, and that she will keep a chest there for your use."
89120236	"<emp>Lothering is lost</emp>

Lothering has been overrun by darkspawn. You do not know whether Ser Arbither Cora has perished or escaped; whatever happened, she did it without your help."
89120237	Knife Edge
89120244	Filthy darkspawn! What have they done to my home?
89120245	"You have accepted a quest concerning Ser Arbither Cora, knight of Lothering."
89120261	May the maker have mercy upon your shrivelled soul!
89120262	Drat! Something must have moved them: I'll have to search.
89120263	Here is your reward for what you've done.
89120264	I don't believe you! You're a bally liar - hand those swords over now!
89120265	Thank you . Here is your reward.
89120266	Templars! Help me!
89120267	"One day you'll face the Maker's justice, you bally thief!"
89120268	<desc>Lie</desc>All he had on him was this medallion.
89120271	"Very well, here you are."
89120273	"No way, you'll have to fight for them."
89120275	<desc>Threaten</desc>You can have his medallion but the swords are mine!
89120277	Ser Bryant
89120279	Ser Varal
89120281	Templar
89120283	"Very well, if you change your mind, I'll be here for a  while."
89120284	"Greetings, have you changed your mind about finding my father?"
89120285	Jolly good show! Maker go with you.
89120286	You don't scare me! You're a bally thief - hand those swords over now!
89120289	"No, I think I've done enough."
89120291	"Yes, I'll go and look now."
89120297	Templar
89120299	Good day to you.
89120301	Ser Arbither Cora is dead.
89120303	Knife Edge DS
89120304	"Ser Arbither Cora's home, near the road to Redcliffe - attacked by darkspawn."
89120306	"Spiders like fresh meat for their spiderlings, don't you know? <desc>Shudder</desc> Anyway, did you find my poor father?"
89120308	What did you mean earlier about eggs hatching?
89120309	You have taken Ser Arbither's swords as your reward for rescuing her.
89120313	Cook
89120320	Spiders & Knives
89120321	A simple job to earn a few coins ... but where's the client?
89120323	I just need to make some preparations first.
826465926	I do hope Ser Bryant is safe. He's awfully brave!
826465927	"Welcome to Knife Edge Manor. We've not cleared all the bally mess yet, but the elves are working jolly hard."
826465928	Hail friend! The chest in the Hunter's Room is for your use.
826465931	"Lothering has fallen! Ser Bryant is here, but so many have died!"
826465932	Filthy darkspawn! Why does the Maker allow this?
826465933	Welcome to Knife Edge Manor. For the moment we are safe here.
826465934	"Hail! It's good to see a friend, even in these sad times."
826465943	The Crane. Not much is known about this sword other than it has a twin sword called the Crow. It is said that together they unveil their true power.
826465944	The Crane. Not much is known about this sword other than it has a twin sword called the Crow. It is said that together they unveil their true power.
826465945	The Crow and the Crane are among the less well known artifacts of Ferelden. Both imbued with powerful magic and when wielded together they are said to make their wielder almost invincible.
826465946	The Crow and the Crane are among the less well known artifacts of Ferelden. Both imbued with powerful magic and when wielded together they are said to make their wielder almost invincible.
826465954	Ser Arbither Cora
826465955	"Very aristocratic, maybe a little snooty, but she looks tough, with a slightly wild glint in her eyes."
826465957	"Lothering has fallen! Ser Bryant is here, but so many have died!"
826465958	Filthy darkspawn! Why does the Maker allow this?
826465959	Welcome to Knife Edge Manor. For the moment we are safe here.
826465960	"Hail! It's good to see a friend, even in these sad times."
826465962	I do hope Ser Bryant is safe. He's awfully brave!
826465963	"Welcome to Knife Edge Manor. We've not cleared all the bally mess yet, but the elves are working jolly hard."
826465964	Hail friend! The chest in the Hunter's Room is for your use.
826465972	"Maker willing, this place should be somewhere for the templars to fall back to when Lothering falls."
826465973	"This place is bally filthy! I must get some servants in, those elves are so good at cleaning!"
826465974	"I do hope you'll pop in when we're ship-shape again, old chap. I'll put a chest in the Hunter's Room for your use."
826466002	Good day to you.
826466055	"You have helped Ser Arbither Cora defend Knife Edge. She has indicated that you are welcome to return at any time, and that she will keep a chest there for your use."
826466056	Knife Edge
826466065	Oh you hero! What wonderful timing the maker has!
826466066	Darkspawn are coming! Prepare yourself; they'll be here any second!
826466075	"Oh my, that was a hard fought battle. Jolly well done!"
826466076	"Isn't Ser Bryant wonderful! So brave, and so handsome!"
826466077	Isn't Ser Bryant wonderful!
826466078	"Ser Bryant and I are to be married once this is all over, Maker willing!"
826466079	Please come to our wedding!
826466080	"Hail! It's good to see a friend, even in these sad times."
826466081	"Hail friend, welcome to Knife Edge Manor! The chest in the Hunter's Room is for your use."
826466090	Did you just...?
826466091	The people here have precious little. That so many resort to thievery makes matters all the worse.
826466092	"So stop it, right now."
826466093	"We are watching you carefully, stranger. Very carefully."
826466103	Please do not cause a disturbance. Matters are delicate enough with all the newcomers.
826466104	We are here to guard this chantry and all mankind from forbidden magics.
826466105	"You are welcome here, so long as you cause no trouble."
826466106	There is something... odd about you. I trust that you are not here to make trouble.
826466107	"Greetings, and welcome to the chantry."
826466117	"There's word of darkspawn stragglers, but no sign of the main horde."
826466118	"We are the only hope of protection this village has now, and I will <emp>not</emp> abandon them."
826466119	That is all. May the Maker have mercy on us.
826466126	"I see you have returned, Sister. I thought you had left the chantry for good."
826466127	"I have, Ser Bryant."
826466128	I see. Is there something more I can do for you?
826466129	"And who is the lady with you, if I might ask?"
826466130	"And who is the gentleman with you, if I might ask?"
826466132	"Greetings, Grey Warden. What can I do for you?"
826466133	"Hello, again. What can I do for you?"
826466135	"Yes, my lady? Who might you be?"
826466136	"I... see. I am Ser Bryant, commander of the Lothering templars."
826466137	"Teyrn Loghain declared all Grey Wardens traitors, responsible for the king's death. You know this, I hope?"
826466138	And set a bounty on any who survived.
826466139	"I don't believe the Grey Wardens would be as careless or malicious as the teyrn claims, but either way, there it is."
826466140	"It is best you not linger, though. Just... in case."
826466141	"Even if I had no other concerns, I would not seek to collect the bounty."
826466142	"I am Ser Bryant, commander of Lothering's remaining templars."
826466143	You don't seem like the other refugees. Are you one of Arl Eamon's knights?
826466144	I'd tell you what I told the others: Nothing here will assist your quest. The Urn of Sacred Ashes is a myth.
826466145	A mythical relic of Andraste.
826466146	"One of the arl's knights, Ser Donall, is here searching for fantasies while…"
826466147	Never mind. Ask him if you care about this foolishness.
826466148	"If the matter is important, certainly."
826466149	The revered mother leads this flock; I merely command her templars.
826466150	"Normally, our role is to protect the chantry and seek out unsanctioned magic. For now, it is all we can do to protect the innocent."
826466151	As am I.
826466152	<desc>Sigh</desc> I have no time to even think about such things right now.
826466153	My concern is protecting these people. I see nothing threatening them other than the darkspawn.
826466154	"Let us pretend that I was such a mage. What would you do to me, hmm?"
826466155	"We have more than swords at our disposal. We are taught to dispel unholy magics, as well."
826466156	If only our powers worked to keep away the darkspawn. Alas it is not so.
826466157	"In her study, no doubt, preparing what she will take when we eventually evacuate."
826466158	"Our bann was summoned by Teyrn Loghain, and he took his soldiers north with him. Lothering has been abandoned."
826466159	"You have met her? She came to the chantry years ago, to begin a new life of contemplation."
826466160	"Yesterday, however, she packed up and left the chantry. Forever, she said."
826466161	"I assume she was fleeing the darkspawn, like the rest of us."
826466162	I don't think her life before she arrived was a happy one.
826466163	"She was never well suited to the life here, but I do believe her faith in the Maker was sincere."
826466164	Of course.
826466169	Other than the darkspawn horde bearing down on us?
826466170	"None of it is good. Teyrn Loghain is set to declare himself king, I hear. Disaster piled on disaster."
826466171	"Teyrn Loghain has no legitimate claim on the throne. He may be a hero, and his daughter may be queen, but he is a commoner and the king's corpse is barely cold."
826466172	"If Arl Eamon was able to intervene, perhaps it would not have gone this far."
826466173	I do not care who takes the throne. Only fools fight over who owns a cottage while it burns down around them.
826466174	None that we know of.
826466175	"I suppose since you are a mage, I do know something that might interest you."
826466176	Don't look surprised. I would be a poor templar if I couldn't tell that much.
826466177	"I have heard word that the templars who watch over the Circle of Magi's tower have called for the Right of Annulment. Hopefully, I've heard wrong."
826466178	"If the Right of Annulment is invoked, the tower and every living soul within will be destroyed."
826466179	We need the Circle's help. We should go and find out what's happening.
826466180	Is one of the treaties not with these mages? 'Twould be ironic to have them fricasseed just when they are useful.
826466181	"To have such a call when mages are needed to fight the darkspawn, something terrible must have happened."
826466182	I have nothing else to tell you. The only news <emp>I</emp> care about is the approaching horde.
826466183	Only if you are interested in the business of mages.
826466184	"They are. With the bann having taken his men north, the village is left to its fate."
826466185	We will evacuate as many as we can before the horde reaches us. I will stay as long as I am needed.
826466186	I... see. That is certainly worthy of notice.
826466187	"I cannot openly help you, I fear, but... here, take this key."
826466188	"It opens the large cabinet on the far wall. There is more there than we can carry when we evacuate, so take what you need."
826466189	Maker's breath! How many times must we drive them off?!
826466190	"Well, you won't find it here. We can barely keep control inside the village, much less on the roads. But I will try once more."
826466191	I will not let them take any more advantage of this catastrophe!
826466192	Ser Varal! Those fool bandits have returned. Take some men and drive them off. And see if you can't capture that leader of theirs this time.
826466193	"As you command, Ser Bryant!"
826466194	"Now, unless there's something else you need...?"
826466195	No need. I will have it dealt with... again.
826466196	Indeed? They're gone?
826466197	"It's true. I saw the bastard running for the hills, myself."
826466198	"That's an impressive feat, indeed! Will you accept a small reward for your efforts?"
826466199	"I wish I could afford such help, to be truthful. Take your reward, at any rate... it is all I have to offer."
826466200	"If it interests you, there is a chanter's board outside full of quests that need doing. The chanters even offer pay for some of them."
826466201	That is very generous of you.
826466202	All of them? By yourself?
826466203	It’s true. I saw it from my post. It was over so fast we didn't even have time to get over there.
826466204	"Sad that it needed to come to that, but then they asked for it. Will you accept a small reward for your service?"
826466205	<desc>Sigh</desc> We can barely keep order here in the village.
826466206	"Travel safely, and may the Maker watch over you."
826466207	"I do, though the priests no doubt would tell you otherwise."
826466208	Then what might I do for you?
826466209	I... see.
826466210	"Some have, in recent days."
826466211	"Arl Eamon has fallen ill, and his knights are on a quest for the sacred urn filled with Andraste's ashes, said to cure any malady."
826466212	Arl Eamon is sick? Is it serious?
826466213	"I'm told it's no natural illness. They have found no cure, and thus must chase after miracles."
826466214	He must be very ill if they chase miracles as the only cure.
826466215	It is no trouble. Maker watch over you.
826466216	Yes? Who might you be?
826466228	I am the Grey Warden <FirstName/>.
826466230	The Grey Wardens did no such thing.
826466231	He claimed we're responsible?
826466234	I've heard the rumors.
826466235	You will say nothing about me. Is that clear?
826466237	You can call me <FirstName/>.
826466239	And if I were?
826466240	Have many of his knights come here?
826466241	What is the Urn of Sacred Ashes?
826466244	I need some information.
826466245	Are you in charge here?
826466247	You do know that I am a mage?
826466250	And if you found an unsanctioned mage?
826466252	How do templars fight against magic?
826466254	Where would I find the revered mother?
826466255	Are you the only protection this village has?
826466256	Tell me about something else.
826466257	Can you tell me of Sister Leliana?
826466259	Do you know why she left?
826466260	What kind of person is she?
826466262	Thank you.
826466267	Have you heard any recent news?
826466269	What do you mean?
826466272	What is wrong with Arl Eamon?
826466273	You think there will be civil war?
826466274	King Cailan had no heir?
826466276	Most people consider Teyrn Loghain a hero.
826466277	Have you heard any other news?
826466280	I already know all about this.
826466281	But that means...
826466286	Why? What is the Right of Annulment?
826466287	Do you know why?
826466288	Now? That seems like odd timing.
826466289	I am. Tell me.
826466290	Not really.
826466291	I've nothing else to ask.
826466292	Things seem very dire in the village.
826466295	I'm hoping you can help me. I'm a Grey Warden.
826466297	Is there any other help you can offer?
826466299	About those bandits outside the village...
826466300	They robbed me. I demand compensation!
826466302	[Lie] They robbed me. I demand compensation!
826466303	"They're still there, last I saw."
826466307	"I can do that, if you like."
826466309	One less. I drove them off myself.
826466312	"Certainly, thank you."
826466313	"I could keep an eye out for trouble, for the right pay..."
826466316	No need. Your thanks is enough.
826466318	They won't bother you again. I killed them.
826466321	You need to watch the roads more carefully.
826466323	I should go.
826466325	"You think it's a myth, do you?"
826466327	Well I'm not one of his knights.
826466328	"No, I'm not."
826466329	"I'm a Grey Warden, actually."
826466331	Do many of his knights come here?
826466337	Nobody of importance.
826466338	Pardon me. I didn't mean to interrupt.
826466341	Genlock
826466343	Hurlock
826466345	Hurlock Emissary
826466347	Shriek
826466349	Knotwood Staff (Enhanced)
826466350	This gnarled staff's origin can be traced back to the Knotwood Hills. No doubt it once belonged to a hangman's tree or worse; a darkspawn scratching pole!
826466351	Dagger of Ashyera's Followers (Enhanced)
826466352	These daggers - though they're scarce in Ferelden - are commonly wielded by a sect within a petty state of the Free Marches.
826466354	Ser Nathan's Amulet
826466355	This amulet is intricately carved with a coat of arms.
826466356	HjorrMikill (Enhanced)
826466357	"HjorMikill' means GreatSword in an ancient language. 
Protected by the mountains and snow, this sword was probably forged for a King when the elders were young, to protect in troubled times."
826466358	Thunderer (Enhanced)
826466359	The unusual design of this heavy one-handed weapon appears to be of foreign origin. The air around the head of the weapon crackles with electrical energy.
826466360	"You were brave too, of course."
826466361	"Here, let me give you my father's amulet: it will protect you in your adventures."
826466375	Lothering has fallen! You wonder if Ser Arbither Cora's manor has been overrun too. Maybe you should pay her a visit?
826466377	Ser Arbether and Ser Bryant played their part in the Battle of Denerim. Both survived and they were subsequently married. Knife Edge has become a popular stopping off point for dwarven merchants.
826466378	"When Lothering fell to the darkspawn, Ser Bryant and his men were able to withdraw to Knife Edge. However they were unable to fight off subsequent darkspawn incursions, and the manor's defenders were all slaughtered."
